<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hackathon on Carlos López Romero</title><link>https://calo001.github.io/tags/hackathon/</link><description>Recent content in hackathon on Carlos López Romero</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://calo001.github.io/tags/hackathon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My participation in the Appwrite Hackathon on DEV 2022</title><link>https://calo001.github.io/p/my-participation-in-the-appwrite-hackathon-on-dev-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://calo001.github.io/p/my-participation-in-the-appwrite-hackathon-on-dev-2022/</guid><description>About the event The Appwrite Hackathon on DEV was announced on April 12th and consisted of building an application under one set of categories. One of those categories was Mobile apps, and in order to participate, I created an app using their SDK and I created a post on the Dev.to where it should include a description of the project, public repository and evidence of how it works.
🔗 More info about the event</description></item><item><title>My participation in the AristiComp 2021</title><link>https://calo001.github.io/p/my-participation-in-the-aristicomp-2021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://calo001.github.io/p/my-participation-in-the-aristicomp-2021/</guid><description>About the event I participated in the AristiComp 2021. It was a competition organized by the content creator and Android developer AristiDevs. The hackathon consisted in creating an app around a topic, the topic was the word &amp;ldquo;Help&amp;rdquo;.
🔗 Details about AristiComp 2021
My participation I build an app called Hazel, with the purpose of helping people to learn English vocabulary using an app where they can search, learn and discover words and phrases.</description></item><item><title>My participation in The Epic Hashnode Writeathon 2022</title><link>https://calo001.github.io/p/my-participation-in-the-epic-hashnode-writeathon-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://calo001.github.io/p/my-participation-in-the-epic-hashnode-writeathon-2022/</guid><description>About the event The Epic Hashnode Writeathon 2022 was a challenge for write an article that would help to solve big technical problems, get started with a programming language or framework, or other developers become 10x better.
There were four categories:
Web apps Mobile apps Cloud computing Web3 🔗 See more about the event
My participation I participated writing an article about how to integrate in the same app the Google Mobile Services and the Huawei Mobile Services.</description></item><item><title>My participation in the HUAWEI Developers LATAM: Winter Contest 2021</title><link>https://calo001.github.io/p/my-participation-in-the-huawei-developers-latam-winter-contest-2021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://calo001.github.io/p/my-participation-in-the-huawei-developers-latam-winter-contest-2021/</guid><description>About the event Huawei invited developers from Mexico, Peru, Chile, and Colombia to participate in the HUAWEI Developer Latinoamérica Winter Contest 2021 to win amazing prizes. It consisted of creating an app and publishing it on the AppGallery additionally the app must integrate at least one of the HMS (Huawei Mobile Services) kits.
🔗 Details about HUAWEI Developers LATAM: Winter Contest
🔗 Details about HUAWEI Developers LATAM: Winter Contest (Facebook)</description></item></channel></rss>